<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<idPkg:Story xmlns:idPkg="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/idml/1.0/packaging" DOMVersion="8.0">
	<Story Self="u3c94" AppliedTOCStyle="n" TrackChanges="false" StoryTitle="$ID/" AppliedNamedGrid="n">
		<StoryPreference OpticalMarginAlignment="false" OpticalMarginSize="12" FrameType="TextFrameType" StoryOrientation="Horizontal" StoryDirection="LeftToRightDirection" />
		<InCopyExportOption IncludeGraphicProxies="true" IncludeAllResources="false" />
		<ParagraphStyleRange AppliedParagraphStyle="ParagraphStyle/Chapter Headings">
			<CharacterStyleRange AppliedCharacterStyle="CharacterStyle/$ID/[No character style]">
				<Content>Chapter 1 23,000 Miles Above the Colorado Rocky Mountains</Content>
				<Br />
			</CharacterStyleRange>
		</ParagraphStyleRange>
		<ParagraphStyleRange AppliedParagraphStyle="ParagraphStyle/MainBodyText">
			<CharacterStyleRange AppliedCharacterStyle="CharacterStyle/$ID/[No character style]">
				<Content>Captain Janice Baker stared absently through the viewport, as the fiery symphony of the universe played out before her tired eyes. After a few moments she sighed and turned away, as if such grandeur had no place in her normal day-to-day life. “Three more weeks,” she moaned under her breath. “Just three more weeks on this spinning wagon wheel. God I hate this damn station.” </Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>She looked up quickly to see if anyone else had overheard her little confession, but her concern was unnecessary, the only other warm body in Central Operations was Ensign Frank Fox: Phoenix Project’s chief engineer. Frank never heard anything except the siren call of his computers. Janice sighed again and returned to her workstation. It was going to be a long three weeks.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>As Captain Baker toiled away, Station Phoenix floated silently above the multicolored patchwork surface of the Earth. Her exterior was a compact mass of dish antennas, receivers and solar collectors; all designed to keep her electronically linked to the seven hundred orbiting drone satellites that monitored and controlled the complicated weather patterns of Terra Firma.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>It wasn’t an easy task; however, Phoenix had performed her duties with distinction for over seventy-five years. Her silver-gray surface showed the effects of sun, extreme exposure to the cold vacuum of space, and over a century of constant bombardment by micrometeorites. Nevertheless, she had been designed well and there was no thought of replacing her.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Captain Baker’s orders were simple: Continue to maintain that level of efficiency while, at the same time, keeping operational costs to a bare minimum. Climatek, like most businesses, lived and died on its bottom line.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>It was rumored that the first Climatek operations manager to be involved in a major weather snafu would be shown the airlock... without the benefit of an environmental suit.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Currently, Janice’s cool sea-gray eyes were directed to her display terminal. It was Monday, and that meant a boring review of the weekly weather schedule. Athletically slender with straight blond hair cut short, she presented an appearance of a much younger woman. In truth, she was in those changeable years before the onset of sixty, when one day you wake up, look at yourself in the mirror and come to the ultimate conclusion that somewhere down the line, life had inescapably passed you by. The only sounds came from the soft humming of the computers, and her chief engineer’s incessant singing.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Janice reached up, massaged her temples and gave Frank a hard practiced stare. A stare that could freeze a crewmember in mid small talk, and send them into instant retreat.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Frank, stared back, smiled and went into his third rendition of the ancient Gene Kelly favorite: Singing in the Rain. He was tall, slender, bordering on anemic, with a mop of unkempt straight black hair that fell halfway to his shoulders—a style currently having a resurgence on Earth. His twenty-eight year old piercing black eyes seemed to always to be saying: What kind of trouble can I get into now? </Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Yet in spite of those qualities, Janice had to admit, he was a good engineer, one of the best she had ever served with. Not that he would ever hear those words coming from her lips. Officially, he was undisciplined, prone toward mischief and totally unprofessional.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Ensign Fox was definitely in his own world. In-between verses of song, he was stuffing his mouth with a strange snack food that closely resembled blue cotton balls—something he had undoubtedly found laying around the station. Frank spent his off hours exploring the old hulk for junk and spare parts.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Phoenix had a long history. In its one-hundred-plus years of service it had been everything from a genetics lab, to an orbiting hotel in the Hilton chain. Climatek, it’s current owners, picked up the station as salvage from the Space Administration almost a century ago, and converted her into a testing lab for an experimental form of global weather control.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Janice frowned again and tried, without much success, to block out Frank’s singing. After six long months, she thought she would have gotten used to it by now... he did it every time they went over the weekly rain schedule. She touched the screen to pause the display, and took a moment to glance through the viewport.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>After three quarters of a century living in a computer-controlled, climate-regulated paradise, they sure were getting to be a bunch of spoiled brats. If the rains didn’t come when promised, the farmers bitched. If the sun didn’t shine at the appointed hours, everyone else moaned and groaned. Janice smiled to herself. Life in a computerized greenhouse sure was hard.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>A high-pitched beep coming from the main computer distracted her reverie. She extracted herself from her chair, walked over to the display and stared at the black numeric figures scrolling across the screen. Halfway down the list, one of the columns turned red. It only took her five seconds to understand what was happening.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Frank, get over here,” she said quickly, still staring at the data screen. “Now!”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Unfortunately the urgency in her voice was totally lost on Frank, who was still encased in his private little world. He was singing loudly and stuffing his face with more blue cotton balls.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Janice closed her eyes and began a slow count to ten. By the time she reached seven, she stopped and requested a hardcopy of the information on her screen. Crumpling the paper into a tight ball, she took aim and threw it at Frank’s head. He stopped singing in mid-verse.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Hey!” he yelled. “What’s the hell’s the matter with you? Don’t you like my singing anymore?” Reaching down, he picked up the offending missile and was about to throw it back, when Janice held up her hand.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Wait a minute,” she said sternly. “Read it before you throw it back at me. And next time pay attention when I call you, Ensign.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>In a silent protest, Frank furrowed his eyebrows into a tight frown and smoothed the crumpled sheet out on his console. He knew better than to open his mouth too wide. When Captain Baker used his rank instead of his name, she usually meant business. Yet, it was beyond his nature to leave the situation totally alone. “Hell of a communication system, Captain,” he said under his breath. “Why don’t you inform the suits down at Climatek? They might be able to use it for inter-station memos.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Shut up and read it,” she returned, becoming more irritated at her chief engineer than usual. “And try to pay attention when you get to the part about Delta Sector.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Frank mumbled something under his breath and concentrated on the paper. Janice thought she caught the word, bitch. After a few seconds he raised his eyebrows and pulled a hand through his coal black hair. </Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“OK, OK... I see it. Temperature over Southern Africa up by point-zero-two.” He shook his head. “You know this is the second time in the last month we’ve had trouble with that orbital controller over Delta Sector. I told you last week we needed to send a maintenance drone over to check it out. It’s one of the new power couplings those idiots dirt-side sent up last month. I’ll bet they didn’t pay one damn bit of attention to the design changes I recommended.” He looked at the data again and scratched his head. </Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Ya know something… This could grow into a real problem if it’s not corrected soon.” That said, he turned around and checked his displays. Ten seconds later, he was singing again.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Janice took a deep breath and released it in a controlled sigh. Ensign Fox had a unique talent for understating the obvious. Plus he knew how to push her buttons. At times she tolerated his insubordination; however, today she was not in the mood.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Did I hear you say this might grow into a problem, Ensign?” She stopped and waited for a response. When none was forthcoming, she continued. “You know as well as I do that if the temperature increases by much more, it’s going to start drawing cool, moist air from the northern part of the continent. They’re not due for cloud formations until next Friday. If that damn controller stops functioning altogether, it could screw up the weather patterns over Africa for weeks. We could....” Suddenly, Janice stopped talking and turned pale. Frank noticed that her eyes seemed glazed, and they seemed to be focused on a spot over his right shoulder.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Uh, you OK, Captain?” he said in an uncertain voice. “You, uh, want a glass of water or something?” He fished around his back for the bag of snacks he had been consuming. “ Here,” he said awkwardly. “Try one of these.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Janice came back to reality and pushed the bag away in disgust.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“President Mogato of Zambia,” she responded faintly. “He’s giving a speech in Johannesburg tomorrow. Don’t you remember? It’s on our monthly hot list: The two-hundredth anniversary of the incorporation of South Africa into the League of African States. One week of blue skies and sunshine to commemorate the event.” Janice stopped and tried to think. “We’ve got to fix this fast or we’ll be digging ore out of the Copernicus mines until the sun turns into a snowball.”</Content>
				<Br />
			</CharacterStyleRange>
		</ParagraphStyleRange>
		<ParagraphStyleRange AppliedParagraphStyle="ParagraphStyle/MainBodyText">
			<CharacterStyleRange AppliedCharacterStyle="CharacterStyle/$ID/[No character style]">
				<Content>Frank leaned slowly back in his chair. “Only one way to do that, Captain,” he said with a grin.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Janice gave him a stern look. “I know... I know. And you’re loving every minute of it, aren’t you?”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Frank ignored the remark and walked over to the main computer. With a dramatic flare, he placed his left hand on a circular metallic disk embedded in the left wall. “Any particular time you’re ready,” he responded with a look of anticipation on his face. Frank always loved it when the computer fouled something up. It gave him a chance to play with the big machine.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Captain Baker walked to the other side of the computer and placed her hand on a similar disk.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Palm scans verified,” the computer responded. “Please state desired program.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Janice glanced over at Frank, who was grinning ear to ear, and shook her head.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Computer...” she said evenly. “This is Captain Janice Baker. Request override of weather-control program for sector Delta.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>The computer responded unemotionally. “Does the chief engineer concur?” </Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Yes,” Frank quickly replied. “Hell, yes!”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Janice gave him a sidelong glance.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>He shrugged. “Sorry about that. It’s been a long day.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Override procedure initiated,” the computer interrupted. “Please enter security codes.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>They removed their hands and proceeded to type the proper codes on small inset touch-pads located next to the disks.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Frank pulled a small scrap of paper out of his pocket and tried to shield it from her view. He wasn’t successful.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Dammit, Frank!” she yelled. “You know you’re not supposed to write those codes down.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“I know... I know,” he responded with a sigh. “But they change the damn combination twice a day. Hell, how’s a guy supposed to remember the latest code?”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>She grabbed the paper out of his hand, ripped it up and threw the pieces into the vaporizer. There was a flash of light and a small puff of white smoke, indicating that the dictates of security had been met. “You know as well as I do that this station controls the weather patterns for the entire globe. What do you think would happen if some nut broke in here and got a hold of this paper?”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Frank watched the smoke rise to the ceiling and disappear into a ventilation grate. </Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Yeah, right,” he responded sarcastically. Like someone is going to waltz twenty three thousand miles up here and knock on the front door. Hell, that’s the major reason they stuck us on this floating donut in the sky. Besides,” he shrugged, “That security hatch over there is two-feet of poly-alloy composites and it can only be opened from the inside. On top of all that, they would still need your command code to finish the sequence.” He shrugged. “Me, why I’d probably tell my access code before they even started the torture. But you... I bet you’d let them hack you to pieces before you’d ever talk.” </Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Frank stopped and shook his head. “Hell, I don’t even know why we’re having this conversation,” he added with a frown. “Earth has known peace for over a half century. Nobody even remembers this station is up here... except when it doesn’t work,” he added with a grin.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Janice wanted to slap that smile to the other side of his face.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“What about the Kolorah?” Janice countered.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“What about them?”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Don’t you think they’d love to get their hands on this station?”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Frank laughed out loud. “Come on, Captain. The Kolorah are an obscure, dying sect. They live the in North and South Polar regions, the only areas not controlled by our computers. So what if they occasionally come down to warmer latitudes and attack an outpost or two. Hell, they don’t even believe in modern technology. How the hell are they supposed to get up here... in a hot air balloon?” He laughed again. “The Kolorah don’t like us because we changed the weather. They think the whole thing is sacrilegious, and an offense to their gods. If they’re the reason we have to change these damn security codes twice a day, then I say, to hell with ‘em. It’s never gonna’ happen. Besides, we wouldn’t even be up here now, if Earth hadn’t played so hard and fast with the eco-system two centuries ago.” He stopped and pointed an accusing finger at the digitized map of the globe. They screwed up the weather patterns with their pollution and ozone-killing gasses, not me. I don’t see why I have to be stuck up here on this orbiting junk pile because of their mistake.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Janice had heard all this before. “It doesn’t matter who’s at fault, all that’s academic now, but if we mess up, we could...”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Could what?” he interrupted. “Make it rain on someone else’s parade? Come on. This station has been here for a long, long time and nothing bad has happened yet.” </Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>He was stopped by a beep from the diagnostic computer.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Janice leaned over and checked the readout. “Oh this is just dandy,” she said with a rising edge of frustration to her voice. “The temperature over Southern Africa has risen another point. That damn power coupling must have failed completely. I suggest you skip the poor-little-me speech and use the remaining drones to increase the density factor over sector Delta by two-point-three to compensate.” She looked over at Frank, who was taking the problem with his usual indifference. “How you ever got assigned up here is way beyond me.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Frank just smiled. “My father owns the company,” he responded with a laugh. “If I want it to snow in Alaska, all I have to do is push a button.” He made a motion as if he were actually going to do it.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Janice grabbed his hand. “Enough Ensign... Stop it right now. You know full well it hasn’t snowed in Alaska for over seventy-five years.” She almost smiled, but caught herself before Frank noticed. “I really don’t think they’d know how to handle it,” she finally responded.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“But just once,” he responded seriously, “wouldn’t it be fun to see?”</Content>
				<Br />
			</CharacterStyleRange>
		</ParagraphStyleRange>
		<ParagraphStyleRange AppliedParagraphStyle="ParagraphStyle/MainBodyText">
			<CharacterStyleRange AppliedCharacterStyle="CharacterStyle/$ID/[No character style]">
				<Content>“Ensign,” she said in that tone usually reserved for crewmembers becoming too friendly. “There is such a thing as responsibility. And the fact that your father helped design this station doesn’t make this place your own personal play toy.” She pointed over to the map. “Earth hasn’t seen bad weather in a long time. Hell, they don’t even make heating systems anymore. Those people depend on us to do it right.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“I know,” he sighed, “but... just once.”</Content>
				<Br />
			</CharacterStyleRange>
		</ParagraphStyleRange>
		<ParagraphStyleRange AppliedParagraphStyle="ParagraphStyle/MainBodyText">
			<CharacterStyleRange AppliedCharacterStyle="CharacterStyle/$ID/[No character style]">
				<Content>She shook her head. “If I thought you were even halfway serious, I’d throw you out the airlock myself... without an environmental suit,” she added under her breath.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>A burst of static from the communication console, brought both of them back to reality.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Phoenix, this is Farmboy... On final approach… Prepare to receive clearance code.” There was a pause. “Err, hello Phoenix? Who’s minding the store? Over.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Saved by the bell,” Frank laughed. </Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Janice wasn’t amused. “Get on that South African problem. I don’t like having the main computer system unlocked for this long.” She moved over to the communication console and sat down. “An hour late,” she remarked over her shoulder to Frank. “That’s got to be some kind of record.” She grabbed the headset and keyed the transmitter. </Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Glad you could make the party, Dave. Clearance code confirmed, ready to receive visual conformation.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>There was a moment of silence. “Negative, Janice. Flight deck cameras are on the blink… again.” Another moment of silence. “You know the company game,” he continued. “You put in a work order for repairs and if it isn’t life threatening, maybe it gets done next work cycle, or maybe not. We lost an hour trying to fix it ourselves, but no luck.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“I could put on a suit and wave to you from one of the external monitors, if that’s what you want, luv.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Janice paused. It was a company regulation that all incoming shipments be verified with a visual. “Hell,” she said out loud, “this is all I need, one more damn problem.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Come on luv,” he interrupted. “I’ve got a hot cargo here. Be a shame to turn around because of a broken camera. The boys at the top wouldn’t like that very much. Extra trip back here...the fuel and overtime. What’d ya say? Open the door and let daddy in.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Janice cut the transmission, leaned back in her chair and let out a controlled sigh. This is not how she had envisioned her life turning out. Two years ago, she had volunteered for training at Gamma Base in the Copernicus Crater. They were the lead group spearheading the activation of the new Mars colony: The first off world installation to be constructed by robotic labor. Unfortunately her application had been pushed back, others had been selected first, now she was still three weeks away from acceptance.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Janice frowned. If she sent Farmboy back home, Climatek probably wouldn’t be happy. Publically they would accept her decision, but privately.... well, that was another matter. Like any other company, Climatek lived and died by its bottom-line. That, coupled with the problem she was currently experiencing over South Africa, might just be enough to tip the scales against her. The United Space Agency might pass on her application again. Janice was fifty-seven, with still a lot of good years ahead of her. But to be stuck on this damn weather station with Frank for the rest of her career was more than she was prepared to take. </Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Three weeks, she kept reminding herself. Just three more damn weeks and then, Mars. That would be it for Janice. She would spend the last seventy or so odd years of her life helping to bring life to a dead planet. She would be happy... she would die happy. </Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Janice rubbed the back of her neck and looked over at Frank. </Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>He shrugged as if to say, it’s your problem, not mine, and returned to his work.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Oh, all right, Farmboy,” she finally answered. “I’d rather not see that ugly mug of yours anyway. Make your docking at bay twelve. And hurry-up,” she added in a voice loud enough for Frank to hear. “I think Ensign Fox is getting space happy.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Frank ignored the remark. He was hunched over his terminal interface, humming to himself, lost in a world of electronics and computer code that was all his. After ten minutes he raised his head, pushed the hair out of his face and smiled. “Program corrected,” he said in triumph. “I’ve bumped a controller from Delta Five into the area and raised the field density by two-point-three... as per your orders,” he added with flair. “Automatics will take over as soon as the temperature stabilizes. After that, I don’t think we’ll...”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>He was stopped in mid-sentence by an ear splitting alarm.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Janice, who had been watching over his shoulder as he methodically attacked the problem, had been bored into her own little world. The alarm jolted her into instant alertness. </Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Breach in the outer hallway!” she yelled. “Lock the system down. Now!!” All she could think of was Dave, Farmboy, and what a fool she had been.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>In compliance to her order, Frank ran over to the main computer, but it was too late. The heavy security hatch blew apart in an explosion of fire and shrapnel. A piece of debris struck his chest, and Ensign Frank Fox collapsed to the deck in a mass of blood and twisted limbs. A bubbling pool of red ran down his chest and slowly began spreading across the blue-carpeted floor. His breathing became short and rapid. A stream of blood spread across his lips and ran down his cheek. His face, which had carried an initial look of shock and pain, was replaced a few seconds later by a cold sightless stare.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>The force of the explosion hurled Janice hard against the far bulkhead. She lay there for a moment like some discarded rag doll. In her mind, she was wondering what was going to happen next... and what, if anything, she would be able do about it. </Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>As her eyes slowly began to focus, she saw three men wearing leather garments enter through the shattered security hatch. Each had a small star tattooed under his left cheekbone, and two of them were carrying what looked like ancient crossbows.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Janice’s head was throbbing and she was fairly certain that her right arm was broken. Still she couldn’t hide the awe in her voice.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Kolorah!” she said in disbelief.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>The third man was taller than the other two and carried no visible weapon. Although he was dressed similar to the others, he wore a floor-length fur cape, dyed blood red, and his blond hair was cut to the traditional shoulder length of the Kolorah high priests. The star on his cheekbone showed a small red drop of blood under the bottom point. If memory served her, that indicated he was a member of the ruling party.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Without a word being spoken, one of the men walked over and checked the body of her former chief engineer. Another came over and forcibly dragged her to her feet. The pain in her right arm was unbearable.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>In silence, the leader moved with slow confidence over to the main terminal. </Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Computer,” he began in a deep voice. “I require access to global override. Please comply.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Global override requires class twelve security,” the computer responded unemotionally. “Please insert activator card and enter clearance code.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Janice laughed. “You’re crazy if you think you can get that kind of clearance.”</Content>
				<Br />
			</CharacterStyleRange>
		</ParagraphStyleRange>
		<ParagraphStyleRange AppliedParagraphStyle="ParagraphStyle/MainBodyText">
			<CharacterStyleRange AppliedCharacterStyle="CharacterStyle/$ID/[No character style]">
				<Content>The cold blue eyes never wavered. Slowly he withdrew a small silver card from his pocket. Janice stopped smiling. </Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Turning around, he inserted the card into the computer and quickly typed a sequence of numbers on the touch-pad.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>To Captain Baker’s utter astonishment, the computer released all of its locks. “That’s impossible,” she said in disbelief. Only two or three people in the world have that code. How could you...”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Before she could finish her question, two men wearing white robes entered the room. But it wasn’t their strange garments that stopped her in mid-sentence. Supported between them on poles, was a white metallic box, three-feet square with a hinged top lid. On its side, emblazoned in bold red lettering, were the words, Radiation Hazard: Property of the United States Army. Janice had seen such devices before; it was a battlefield tactical nuclear weapon. She felt a cold fear run down her spine as she considered what this all might mean.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>The leader acknowledged their presence and turned back to the computer.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Computer,” he began slowly, “increase global field density to maximum.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Request denied,” the computer responded. “Procedure would be harmful to life-forms and is inconsistent with the primary function of this station.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>The man stood silent for a moment. Janice held her breath, waiting to see what would happen next.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Reaching into his pocket, he produced a small voice synthesizer and placed it against his throat. Janice groaned; that must have been how he faked Dave’s voice.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Computer,” he started. “This is General Samuel Morley. Clearance code Alpha-Prime, Sigma, Delta, Omicron. Override safety program and initiate previous order immediately.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>The computer responded without hesitation. “Voice pattern confirmed... Code sequence confirmed... Proceeding with request.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Back on Earth, a confused population looked up as the light from the sun slowly began diminishing. Within fifteen minutes, the noonday sun had been reduced to a ghostly semi-twilight and a cool wind began blowing across the land.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Why are you doing this?” Janice asked plaintively. “Surely you don’t expect to get away with it. They’ll have an armed shuttle up here in no time and the game will be over.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>The leader ignored her and, instead, quickly issued some orders to the two men in white robes. When he was satisfied that all was in order, he slowly turned and faced Janice.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“We have no intention of getting away,” he said with a sneer. “You, and the infidels you serve, have changed the world with your technology. We will now purge the Earth, and when it is over, the Kolorah will rebuild on your graves. Computer!” he yelled. “Lock new program into all orbiting control satellites and disengage.”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Without warning, Captain Baker lunged for the computer’s master lockdown switch. It was a simple mechanism… A straightforward button that, if pressed, even by accident, would lock down the main computer, and restore all of the original weather-control programs. The lockdown would then remain in effect for 24 hours and, in Captain Baker’s mind would more than enough time for Climatek to mount a rescue mission.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Unfortunately, the leader had anticipated her action. In a swift move, he reached out and struck her across the face with a savage backhand. She twisted sideways from the force of the blow and fell to the deck, momentarily dazed. Blood began running from the corner of her mouth and down her cheek, forming red droplets on the floor.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“You will not be allowed to defile this ceremony,” he said calmly. “Behold the instrument of your purification.” As he spoke, one of the men in white removed the bomb’s safety cover. Janice noticed that the detonation timer was set to zero seconds. One push of a button and it would all be over.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>With a deliberate force of will, Janice stood shakily to her feet, wiping the blood from her cheek with the back of her hand. Her right shoulder, down to her elbow, felt like hot fire. She ignored the pain and looked over at the still body of her crew chief. </Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>This can’t be happening, she thought to herself. God in heaven, this can’t be happening.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“Why are you doing this?” She was pleading now. Not for herself, but for the defenseless billions on the planet’s surface below her. “If you destroy this station, it will take months before control can be reestablished to the orbiting satellites. The populations of Earth can’t survive under those conditions. You’re dooming over five billion souls to death by freezing... For God’s sake, man!!”</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>“You are correct,” he responded, a smoldering light growing in his blue eyes. “It is for God’s sake that we are doing this.” </Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>The leader turned and said something in a strange language to the others. One by one, they knelt on the deck and bowed their heads. As she looked on helplessly, he walked over to the bomb and, without the slightest hesitation, pressed the detonator switch.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Janice instinctively tried to shield herself from the blast, but before she could turn away, the scene before her eyes instantly froze. Everything was outlined in a sharp white light emanating from the bomb. Her crew mate, Frank, lying dead on the floor in a pool of blood; the Kolorah, kneeling in front of her in their white robes; and the strange man who had been their leader... all frozen before her eyes like some macabre holographic projection. Then, slowly, everything began to fade. She felt herself being absorbed by the light... consumed by its brightness.</Content>
				<Br />
				<Content>Captain Janice Baker’s last conscious thought wasn’t fear, but amazement at how silent death was... bombs always make noise.</Content>
				<Br />
			</CharacterStyleRange>
		</ParagraphStyleRange>
	</Story>
</idPkg:Story>
